[Music]
today we all want to do things quick and
hassle-free
that's why online shopping has become
more and more popular aside some
shopping for clothes and other products
will shop at FWB
you can actually get insured online so
it's hassle-free a fast affordable and
you can also keep the paperwork's and
other medical requirements so without
further ado let me show you how so on
your phone you visit swb that's from the
th and you go to shop at FWD you can see
it on the banner or the section of the
website and under shop at FWD you'll be
able to see the three candy plus setting
hub so hand you off covers you so you
can do everything you want in life you
don't even so the first slide is on men
it has 100,000 pesos critical illness
coverage and it's 1799 per year and the
second plan it's kinda live it has two
hundred thousand pesos life coverage and
it costs one thousand seven hundred
ninety nine per year and the third man
is
Vanguard it's hot it has 500,000
accident
to enter recent coverage and cost 1799
so you can view each plan by clicking
learn more or you can invite their pubic
by now
so yeah unbend learn more to know
coverage and inclusion
and by not occupied so when you buy the
plan they will ask you for your details
so it starts your personal information
your name date of birth and your contact
details I'll just fill it out
[Music]
and it will also ask for your engine
so also asked for cooler than teens like
he's going to discover one
[Music]
then once they have very pioneer
application you can proceed with payment
by a drug would be can actually be using
Visa or MasterCard they will just ask
you for your card number expiration
thing and CVN of their card exact single
so you just have to pay the total amount
all 1799 so that's it for today's video
I include all the important links down
below so you can check them out so if
you have any questions just leave a
comment so I can answer them thank you
so much for watching and I hope to see
you in the next one bye